<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DeepCode</string>
    <string name="sign_id">ID</string>
    <string name="sign_pw">password</string>
    <string name="sign_up_name">your name</string>
    <string name="sign_up_pwch">same password as above</string>
    <string name="sign_up_pwerr">Passwords do not match</string>
    <string name="pwname">Password</string>
    <string name="signupname">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="pwchName">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="signIn_login">Log In</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_idpqErr">Please check your ID/password</string>
    <string name="toast_login">Login successful</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_signuperr">ID/password do not match. If not a member, please sign up first</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_pwerr">Passwords do not match</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_spaceerr">No spaces allowed in ID, name, or password</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_signup">Registration complete! Available after logging in</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_nameerr">Please enter a name in English or Korean only</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_id2err">Please enter ID in English and numbers only</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_pw2err">Please enter a password with English, numbers, and special characters</string>
    <string name="recuit_item1_user_name">Naver Job Posting</string>
    <string name="recuit_item2_user_name">Kakao Job Posting</string>
    <string name="recuit_item3_user_name">Toss Job Posting</string>
    <string name="recuit_item4_user_name">Woowa Brothers Job Posting</string>
    <string name="recuit_item5_user_name">Samsung Job Posting</string>
    <string name="recuit_item1_text">[Application Period] \n2023.12.29~2024.01.05 \n[Recruitment Process] \nDocument Review>Online Coding Test>1st Interview>Internship>2nd Interview</string>
    <string name="recuit_item2_text">[Application Period] \n2023.12.29~2024.01.05 \n[Recruitment Process] \nDocument Review>Online Coding Test>1st Interview>Internship>2nd Interview</string>
    <string name="recuit_item3_text">[Application Period] \n2023.12.29~2024.01.05 \n[Recruitment Process] \nDocument Review>Online Coding Test>1st Interview>Internship>2nd Interview</string>
    <string name="recuit_item4_text">[Application Period] \n2023.12.29~2024.01.05 \n[Recruitment Process] \nDocument Review>Online Coding Test>1st Interview>Internship>2nd Interview</string>
    <string name="recuit_item5_text">[Application Period] \n2023.12.29~2024.01.05 \n[Recruitment Process] \nDocument Review>Online Coding Test>1st Interview>Internship>2nd Interview</string>
    <string name="recuit_item6_user_name">Letple Project</string>
    <string name="recuit_item7_user_name">Community App for Teens</string>
    <string name="recuit_item8_user_name">China Tourist Travel Assistant App</string>
    <string name="recuit_item9_user_name">Clothing 020 Platform</string>
    <string name="recuit_item10_user_name">Malta Project</string>
    <string name="recuit_item6_text">Reason for Starting the Project\nThis app is a service created from our team\'s experience with side projects over the past few years. Many side projects are looking for people to collaborate with, but the methods were somewhat manual.</string>
    <string name="recuit_item7_text">Reason for Starting the Project\nThis app is a service created from our team\'s experience with side projects over the past few years. Many side projects are looking for people to collaborate with, but the methods were somewhat manual.</string>
    <string name="recuit_item8_text">Reason for Starting the Project\nThis app is a service created from our team\'s experience with side projects over the past few years. Many side projects are looking for people to collaborate with, but the methods were somewhat manual.</string>
    <string name="recuit_item9_text">Reason for Starting the Project\nThis app is a service created from our team\'s experience with side projects over the past few years. Many side projects are looking for people to collaborate with, but the methods were somewhat manual.</string>
    <string name="recuit_item10_text">Reason for Starting the Project\nThis app is a service created from our team\'s experience with side projects over the past few years. Many side projects are looking for people to collaborate with, but the methods were somewhat manual.</string>
    <string name="home_item1_user_name">Bill Gates</string>
    <string name="home_item2_user_name">Elon Musk</string>
    <string name="home_item3_user_name">Mark Zuckerberg</string>
    <string name="home_item4_user_name">Kim Young-han</string>
    <string name="home_item5_user_name">Kim Bum-soo</string>
    <string name="home_item1_text">This year marks the beginning of a new era,\nand the reason to believe that next year presents an opportunity to create the next chapter for a better world is right here.</string>
    <string name="home_item2_text">People work better when they know their goals and the reasons behind them.\nIt is essential for people to eagerly look forward to going to work and finding joy in their tasks every morning.</string>
    <string name="home_item3_text">If you believe it\'s right, push through to the end.\nStarting with small tasks can lead to accomplishing great things.\nIn the end, those with conviction emerge victorious.</string>
    <string name="home_item4_text">Leap forward with determination in your steps, contemplation in your heart, and action in your body.\nJust as a tree cannot grow under a larger tree, humans can grow into someone even greater under the guidance of a mentor.</string>
    <string name="home_item5_text">\'Right Time, Right Action\' is crucial.\nBusiness success hinges on taking appropriate actions at the right time.\nMissing the timing renders the effort meaningless.</string>
    <string name="home_myPark_text">Park Min-young</string>
    <string name="profile_my_post_list">My Post List</string>
    <string name="updateProfile_id">ID</string>
    <string name="updateProfile_name">Name</string>
    <string name="updateProfile_update_confirm">Update Complete</string>
    <string name="profile_user_name">Name</string>
    <string name="profile_user_id">ID</string>
    <string name="profile_myPark_text">Park Min-young</string>
    <string name="profile_myPark_id">myPark</string>
    <string name="profile_update_profile">Update Profile</string>
    <string name="profile_following">Following</string>
    <string name="profile_follower">Followers</string>
    <string name="profile_sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="btn_follow_text">Follow</string>
    <string name="btn_unfollow_text">Unfollow</string>
    <string name="detail_item1_text">We are at the starting point of a transition. If you haven\'t figured out how to use AI yet, you are not alone. Just as many people did not use the internet at first, over time, everyone realized the convenience of using email, shopping online, and using search engines. It\'s natural that everyone will use AI one day. One of my favorite innovation stories is that the number of children under 5 who die worldwide has halved since 2000. AI tools can accelerate the pace of drug development. Although there is still a gap, it is much shorter than the gap seen in other technological innovations. With wise investments, AI can make the world a fairer place. When I was young, I didn\'t care about holidays or weekends, but since becoming a father, I realized that there are more important things in life than work. I hope you spend the holiday season with your loved ones before 2024 begins.</string>
    <string name="news_item1_text">McDonald\'s to Introduce Google\'s AI in All Global Stores\nMcDonald\'s has announced the implementation of Google\'s artificial intelligence (AI) technology in all its stores worldwide. While specific details were not disclosed, it appears that AI chatbots will be integrated into kiosks and dedicated mobile apps, with AI technology applied to cameras within the stores. McDonald\'s stated that it will leverage Google\'s hardware, data, and AI technology to provide a better experience for both customers and employees. As part of the partnership, McDonald\'s plans significant developments, ranging from its mobile app used by 150 million people to thousands of self-service kiosks. For more details, click here.</string>
    <string name="news_item2_text">9 Strategies to Keep the Development Team Happy\nThe increasing demand for software developers is no secret, even in uncertain economic conditions. Companies are exerting efforts to find and retain individuals skilled in coding. In such situations, an essential question for development team leaders is understanding the factors that make developers satisfied in their profession. It\'s crucial to identify the issues. In situations where there are many options, developers are less likely to stay in a job that doesn\'t meet their expectations. The job satisfaction of developers takes top priority for every company aspiring to create high-quality software. Various developers and IT professionals were asked about the factors that make developers happy at work. Here are their responses. For more information, click here.</string>
    <string name="news_item3_text">"KakaoT Overseas Call Service Grows Over 7 Times Compared to Last Year"\nKakao Mobility\'s taxi platform, KakaoT, reported significant growth in overseas call service usage during the first quarter of this year, with over 7 times the volume compared to the same period last year. Kakao Mobility revealed this information in an end-of-year report containing various data on KakaoT\'s overseas mobility services. For more details, click here.</string>
    <string name="news_item4_text">The Best Choice for Modernizing IT Infrastructure: \'STaaS\'\nIT infrastructure supports companies in seizing new opportunities and adapting to constantly changing customer demands. With the advent of the era of cloud computing, companies are under pressure to provide a flexible IT infrastructure with features such as continuous operation, unlimited on-demand capacity, and preparedness for operational disruptions and failures. For more information, click here.</string>
    <string name="news_item5_text">Google Settles \'Antitrust Lawsuit\' for 910 Billion Won… Changes in Android Phone Payment Systems\nGoogle has agreed to settle the antitrust lawsuit filed by over 30 U.S. states regarding the alleged coercion of its in-app payment system. Google announced on the 18th (local time) that it will pay a settlement of 7 billion dollars (approximately 910 billion won) to resolve the lawsuit. For more details, click here.</string>
    <string name="news_item1_user_name">AI News</string>
    <string name="news_item2_user_name">IT World News</string>
    <string name="news_item3_user_name">Yonhap News</string>
    <string name="news_item4_user_name">ZDNET Korea</string>
    <string name="news_item5_user_name">World Daily News</string>
    <string name="follower_delete">delete</string>
    <string name="following_unfollow">unfollow</string>
</resources>
